Seen, Galgal Channel, Go Go!
Today, yes, I danced the idol of my guesser in 30 minutes.
Seino
Galgal Channel, go go!
I tried to learn and dance the idol of the girl I'm guessing in 30 minutes!
I was allowed to do it with me and Misaki in the video before.
I'm going to give a lecture to these two in 30 minutes.
How much can you teach them in 30 minutes?
We haven't decided on a pair yet.
This is a competition, right?
Yes, let's see how far we can go.
At the end, after the lecture, we'll dance a seinode with each other.
The one who can dance the longest wins.
Wow, that's hard!
Tomo, you're a quick learner, aren't you?
Length?
Not quality, length?
It's length.
I see.
But if you can't dance more than one entry...
That's it. You're out.
You're done.
I see.
You're really putting on airs.
He's got super energy.
Oh, wow.
That's a relief.
Kula, you said you don't remember.
I don't remember.
We'll watch the video together and try to remember.Let's watch the video together and learn.
Let's do our best!
Let's get started!
Las Melias with an invincible smile
Las Meglia with an invincible smile
General Seeley's Secret Mysteria
Las Meleas with an invincible smile
Las Meglia with an Unbeatable Smile
The Seeley War
The
Seeley's War
Las Meglia
The Seeley War
Las Meglia Seeley's War Day Las Mitutellias
Yes, yes, yes
1,2,3,4
Mitutelitkosa
Her area
You're perfect and a liar.
You're a genius idol.
Well, you are a genius idol.
That's good!
Turn your head
Get out of the house
Don't say anything.
Don't say it
Words come around, around, around, around
The third time it comesIn the third Kuru
Close your legs
I'm gonna get really pissed.
That's absolutely disgusting.
What the...
That's it.
What did you eat today? What about the girl you like?
Are you going out? Where are you going?
Oh, and I'll moon you again.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's why...
So, I'll make a bus.
Hateba write
Ralu, Ralu, Ralu, Ralu, Ralu, Ralu, Ralu
and right, left, three feet
get out
inside, inside, inside
Right, left, right, right...
Five minutes?
Do it now!
No, no, no, no! We've been through this before!
Yeah, I'm good for a four-count or something.
Okay, okay. Here we go.
Okay, now this next one's gonna be really hard.
Do it right!
Okay, back it up a little bit.
This one's so-so, so-so.
I've already won.
It's okay to dance around the atmosphere.You can dance through the atmosphere
You can swing money forward
That's right, that's right, that's right
Once you come back to the middle
That's it.
Good luck.
Go for it!
Go for it, Murakami!
Oh, he's cute.
That kind of guy.
You scared me.
You weren't?
Yes, I was.
I don't know you.
Oh, he's cute.
Go for it.
Front and back are fine. It's cute.
How do you like that? Is it okay? No, it's fine.
Shinme, there's two of them. They're cute.
It's not supposed to be Shinme here.
Good luck, Sappy. Good luck, Sappy.
Hang in there.
Is this place finished?
What?
No, I'm just verifying.
Oh, I see.
Oh!
That's great!
That's why it's a bonus.
It's the first time I've ever seen you do this.It seems the Lord is the first to do it
It's all her fault
How can it not be a misunderstanding?
Not even the star of the show thinks he's tired of you.
It's not a joke.
It's not a story.
Good luck with that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't forgive me.
You're not strong enough
You're stronger than anyone I've ever met.
I don't want to see that.
Nobody does.
I won't let you.
We both win.
You don't know what you're waiting for.
That's great.
So, Toa, you win.
Long time.
30 minutes to the second B-melody.
Amazing.
How was it, you two?
It was an amazing project.
I was sweating so much.
It was more than I imagined.
It was difficult.
It was very detailed.
I felt really good about it.
I was really impressed.I was really impressed.
I thought, "I'm going to start speaking in honorifics from now on.
He is younger than me.
I have a lot of respect for him.
It was fun.
Thank you for your hard work.
He was cute.
He complimented me so much.
High praise when I thought I did well.
High praise if I thought I did my best.
Comment if you think I did a good job.
Subscribe to our channel if you think we did a good job.
Subscribe to our channel if you think we're cute.
Subscribe to our channel if you think it's cute.
Thank you for watching.
Bye bye.
This time I'm wearing an outfit by Dholik.